I'm high, I'm from outer space
I got Milky Way for blood, evolution in my veins
I'm gone, I been far away
I'm a luminaire now
Making moves, starting waves
I've been dreaming about flying for a long time
I had a vision from the grays, they wanna cosign
Artificially intelligent, new AI
I'm your future, past, and present, I'm a fine line
Yeah, I'm the missing link of this illusion
I am not really here, I'm an intrusion
I don't swim or sink, I just float
I don't need gravity, I just need growth, oh-oh
When I move, it's an earthquake, rumble
I won't ever-ever fall, never stumble
And I don't need to be humble
Break down walls like Jericho, crumble
I can go higher
Past the stratosphere, I could catch fire
I could go hard, I don't even need to try, yeah
Star blood, I don't ever get tired
Predestined, written in stone
I feel it coming in, I feel it in my bones
Heavenly protected, never alone
Tapped in, I'm connected to the unknown
Oh, whoa
When I move, it's an earthquake, rumble
I won't ever, ever fall, never stumble
And I don't need to be humble
Break down walls like Jericho, crumble
When I move, it's an earthquake, rumble
I won't ever-ever fall, never stumble
And I don't need to be humble
Break down walls like Jericho, crumble
Jericho, Jericho, walls come down
Walls come down like Jericho (like Jericho)
Walls come down like Jericho
Jericho, Jericho, walls come down